After encoding all our word and label data as an additional preprocessing step,
对所有字词和标签数据进行编码后 还要完成一个预处理步骤
we want to make sure that our reviews are in good shape for standard processing.
我们需要适当地变形影评 使所有影评都标准化
That is, our network will expect a standard input text size,
也就是说 传入网络中的输入文本必须是标准大小
and so we'll want to shape our reviews into a consistent specific length.
所以我们需要将影评变形为一致的长度
There are two things we'll need to do to approach this task.
这个任务分成两步
First, I'm going to take a look at the review data and see do we have
首先检查影评数据中是否有
any especially sure or longer views that might mess with our training process.
会扰乱训练流程的超短或超长影评
I'll especially look to see if we have any reviews of length zero which
例如是否有长度为 0 的影评
will not provide any text information and will just act as noisy data.
这种影评不能提供任何文本信息 只会带来干扰
If I find any of those zero length reviews,
如果发现这种长度为 0 的影评
I'll want to remove them from our data entirely.
需要删除整个影评
Then second, I'll look at the remaining reviews,
第二步是查看剩下的影评
and for really long reviews,
对于超长的影评
I'll actually truncate them at a specific length.
将影评截断到特定的长度
I'll do something similar for shortest reviews and make sure
并对更短的影评执行相似的操作
that I'm creating a set of reviews that are all the same length.
使所有影评的长度都一样
This will be our padding and truncation step,
这就是填充和截断步骤
where we basically pad our data with columns of zeros
即用零列填充数据或删除某些列
or remove columns until we get our desired input shape.
最终获得想要的输入形状
Okay. Before we pad our review text,
Ok在对影评文本进行填充之前
we should check for reviews of length zero.
我们需要检查是否有长度为 0 的影评
The way I'm gonna do this is to use a counter.
我将使用计数器
For each review length that's currently in our data,
对于数据目前具有的各种影评长度
whether that's a length of zero or thousands of words,
无论是长度为 0 还是有数千个字词
I'll look at how many reviews are of that length.
我都会检查有多少条影评是这个长度
So this returns a dictionary of
这行代码返回一个字典 review_lens
review lengths and account for how many our reviews fall into those lengths.
该字典会记录有多少影评长度为这些值
So, here I'm looking at how many of our reviews are
现在查看有多少条影评长度为 0
zero length and I'll also print out the longest review length just to see.
并输出最长影评的长度
So, when I run this cell,
运行该单元格
I can see that I have one review that is zero length
结果显示有 1 条影评的长度为 0
and that my longest review has over 2,000 words in it.
最长的影评包含 2,000 多个单词
This zero length review is just going to add noise into our dataset.
这个长度为 0 的影评对数据集来说没什么用
So next, your task will be to create a new list of
下面你需要创建一个新的 reviews_ints 列表
reviews_ints and an array of encoded labels,
以及一个 encoded_labels 数组
where any reviews of zero length will be removed from this data.
reviews_ints 列表不能包含长度为 0 的影评
So, remove any zero length reviews from
所以请从该列表里删除长度为 0 的影评
reviews_ints and remove that corresponding label as well.
并删除对应的标签
In this particular case, after running this cell,
运行该单元格后
I expect to see that one of our reviews was removed.
结果应该显示 1 个影评被删掉了
Try to solve this task on your own, and next,
快来完成这道练习吧
I'll present my solution and introduce you to your next exercise.
接下来我会介绍我的实现方式并布置下道练习